There is a brother with a red suit. Come here.
Thank You, Jesus!
Ok, it's alright.
Brother, you have an issue with a child. They say the child is not your child.
I have been doubting.
They say the pregnancy is not your own.
Yes.
A woman introduced you to this man.
Yes, sir.
The woman who introduced you is now saying that the child is not for him.
Yes, Man of God.
She told me that someone came to her and told her something like that.
So, that was why she called me last Sunday.
Brother, they are playing games with you.
I lived in Greece for many years.
Why are you afraid that you are not the one?
Because the baby doesn't look like me.
Prophecy Time
Can you see that that question has exposed everything?
Simple.
We need God's wisdom.
Only that question alone - I'm not going to proceed.
I will see them one-on-one.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is James Chineke.
The person beside me is my beautiful and lovely wife.
And this is my son - Emmanuel Chineke.
On last week Sunday during the mass prayer, the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, pointed at my direction.
He prophesied about a man wearing a red suit that he has a controversy concerning a child.
I confirm it to be 100% plus true.
Actually, it was two weeks ago - I was with my wife when my sister called my wife.
She asked her to bring the child and come over to her house.
I asked my wife, "Why is your face like this on the telephone?"
She told me that my sister said that the child is not our child.
I said, "What?" - It was like I was dreaming. I couldn't believe it.
I said, "Can I hear it again?"
"She said it is not our child."
I said, "What?"
At the time, I started asking my wife, "Do you understand what my sister is talking about?"
She said, "No". She was laughing as if we were joking.
I couldn't stand it.
I continued asking her. She still said the same thing.
The next day, I went to see my sister.
I told my sister, "My wife told me about what is happening".
My sister did not even want to talk to me.
She told me, "There are people rumouring around and all this et cetera".
I asked, "About what?"
She said, "They think that the child is not ours. It is someone else's".
My wife started telling my sister that she didn't know what she was talking about.
I also said, "My sister, what do you want us to do about this?"
She told me that the ball was in my court.
That she was waiting for me to do something about that.
When I came here, I was praying (for the man of God to locate me)
because I didn't want to go anywhere else.
I believe so much in The SCOAN.
That God should use Prophet T.B. Joshua to reveal any secret thing.
That God can see me through here.
When I came here, I was praying, "God, I don't want to go anywhere else.
I just want You to see me through Prophet T.B. Joshua. I want him to locate me".
To God be the glory, it was on last week Sunday that the man of God pointed at my direction,
that there was such a thing about a child.
I said to myself, "Ok, it means that what anybody is rumouring about,
now God will show me that He is really God in my family".
The man of God promised us that we will see him one-on-one.
When we went there, he told us that the child is my own child.
Children of God, 'Emmanuel' once more!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
That is my testimony.
Concerning about...
Sorry - I want to apologise to my wife before going on.
She is my beautiful wife and to tell you the truth:
She doesn't know anything about men. I'm even the first man in her life.
I'm telling you the truth.
I'm the first man in her life. She doesn't know any other man. It's true.
So to the glory of God, we want the viewers to understand what you are saying.
You came here last week.
As you were praying, the man of God prophesied about your case
and you came out to confirm the prophecy of the man of God.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
And the man of God said that he will see you.
Yes.
Now, after the prophecy, tell us what happened.
When I went home, I told my sister and my family about it. Everybody was happy.
I'm really happy for this day. Today is one of my happiest days on earth, to tell you the truth.
Everyone was happy.
Even the testimony I'm giving now, I know that they are watching me right now.
Concerning my family: My sister is completely convinced now because of what she heard
from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, about the confirmation of this child.
When I told her about it and also my younger siblings, everybody was very happy.
After the prophecy of the man of God, because of the issue on the ground, that this baby is not yours...
After they had listened to the prophecy of the man of God, they are now convinced and happy.
Yes, they are very happy now.
And what are they saying?
They said, "Ok". Everyone was playing with my son.
They were now happy with my wife and were apologising that what they had said was wrong.
That it was not true and that they were very sorry.
That she should forgive them for everything.
So you are confirming the word of prophecy given by the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua
concerning the baby - that they said that the baby is not yours.
This is just a frame-up, and your family, everybody believes now, apologising to you and your wife,
"Oh, hearing from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, we believe that this baby is yours".
Yes, they believe now that the baby is mine.
Everybody is very happy.
Going by the question the man of God asked you last Sunday,
"What can you say about this issue?",
you said that the baby does not look like you.
What do you have to say now?
I have apologised to my wife. That it was pressure.
I was under pressure and stress.
I'm very sorry for that.
Even though...
Mr & Mrs Chineke
Prophecy Testimony
Put your hands together!
Mr & Mrs Chineke
Prophecy Testimony
So, my wife understands me very well that it was pressure and stress behind all this.
I'm very sorry - once more again.
So everything is settled now. To God be the glory.
Everything is settled.
People of God, let's put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
Mr & Mrs Chineke
Prophecy Testimony
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church!
On last week Sunday, the man of God gave my husband a prophecy concerning our child
which I confirm to be true because two weeks ago, I received a call, as he said,
from his sister concerning the child that the child that they thought was theirs was not.
I was like, "What are you saying? I don't understand". I was just laughing.
I didn't feel that they were accusing me of something like that.
My husband questioned me.
I told him, "Daddy, do you need to ask me this question? Why are you still asking me that one?
I was even angry because of the question he was asking me, "Is it true or not?"
They were supposed to know that it was not true.
Later on, the man of God prophesied about it.
I was so happy because that was one of my prayer points
that God should vindicate me through the man of God.
As he had seen other peoples' problems, he should also see mine because it was an embarrassment to me.
I would never think of doing something like this.
I thank God for last Sunday, that everything was out and open.
I thank God for vindicating me.
Even the comment that he made that the child did not look like him,
I didn't take it as anything because I knew that he was not that kind of man.
I knew it was out of pressure that he made that comment.
At home, he was pleading, begging for forgiveness.
I said, "No problem. I know that it was the devil's handwork.
He wanted to bring sadness into our marriage".
Because all this while - we have been married for two years - we have been so happy.
We have been living like best friends, like brother and sister, and also like husband and wife.
I thank God for everything. I give God all the glory.
Let's put our hands together!
Yes, prophecy with instant solution, and we thank God for your life.
The advice I have for people listening to me:
When you are in fear, doubt or anxiety, or in this kind of situation,
you should not run away from God.
Run to God because He is the one that gives peace of heart, freedom from fear
and liberty from anxiety. Thank you.
Amen.
Mr & Mrs Chineke
Prophecy Testimony
My advice goes to the viewers all over the world:
First of all, I thank God for this testimony, for opening doors, breakthrough and blessings.
More especially my friends watching me right now all over the world,
more especially in Greece:
I want to tell you that these are rumours. They are fake and not real.
When you are experiencing this type of mess - rumours or accusations - please handle it with care.
Don't run from God; run to God. God has the final say.
In my own case, I didn't go anywhere.
Despite the stress and pressure I was experiencing, I didn't think of going outside God.
I came here because I knew that God has the final solution.
Once more, I want to thank God for Prophet T.B. Joshua.
We Nigerians really don't know what we have.
It's a pity. I'm sorry to use that word.
It's a pity. We don't know what we have.
That is my advice.
Let me ask you, sir. If this prophecy had not come, what do you think might have happened to this marriage?
Actually, this question is very important.
It's almost... because I'm a kind of person that does not try such kind of thing.
It would have really been divorce.
100 percent plus divorce.
And once again, people want to hear from you.
What can you say about this baby? Who is this baby?
The baby is mine.
Hallelujah! People of God, put your hands together!
Mr & Mrs Chineke
Prophecy Testimony
Yes, God Almight is the answer to all fundamental issues of life.
We thank God Almighty for what He has done in this family,
and we believe the best is yet to come.
Very soon, we are expecting more of your testimonies. Amen!
Mr & Mrs Chineke
Prophecy Testimony